windowsestimator.com 2015-12-05

# Privacy Policy

#### Our Commitment To Privacy

We at **windowsestimator.com** are committed to respecting your online privacy and recognize your need for appropriate protection and management of any information you share with us by using our web sites. This policy describes what kind of information we collect on **windowsestimator.com** , how we use this information, and your ability of opting-out. Personally Identifiable Consumer Information That We Collect

On certain pages on **windowsestimator.com** , you can submit a request for home improvement quotes from our partner's contractors network. We collect several pieces of information including:

  * Name (first and last name)
  * Project Address (street address, city, state and zip code)
  * Email address
  * Phone number

* * *

#### Non-Personally Identifiable Consumer Information That We Collect

To enhance the user experience on **windowsestimator.com** , we collect data about the visitor computer including operating system, web browser, java script enabling status, IP address, and referral URL. We may use this data to re-market our website to those visitors by launching advertising campaigns on reputable advertising companies.

* * *

#### How Do We Use Your Information?

Once you submit a quote request on our website including the information listed above, we will pass this data in real time to one of our partners. At this moment of our business, we have no contractor network. Such that we work with several reputable partners to match our website visitors with local contractors.

The selection of the partner usually depends on the partner desire to accept quote requests at the time the user submits the request, and on the type of the project.

Once our system selects a partner, we pass the information about the quote request to this partner automatically. The partner will carry out a matching process to determine the most suitable contractors for your project. The matching process depends on many factors including but not limited to the request quote project description determined by the user answers to our form various questions (e.g. install or repair windows). Your quote request usually will be matched to 1-4 contractors. In some cases, the partner will not be able to match your quote with any partner.

* * *

#### Communication After Quote Request Submission

Once the matching process has been carried out, the partner and/or matched contractors will attempt to call or email you. The purpose of the communication is to inform you of who you have been matched to, discuss your project and discuss their service cost. In addition, the partner may utilize such information for marketing purposes, including to contact you about your request and other services that they believe may be of interest to you. **windowsestimator.com** will not attempt to carry out any sort of communication with the individuals who submit quote request since our partner companies will carry out the communication including but not limited to an email confirmation after quote request submission.

* * *

#### Information Sharing

**windowsestimator.com** will share information immediately with our partners, whom in turn, will share your information with their contractor network. After sending your quote request (which includes Personally Identifiable Consumer Information), **windowsestimator.com** will never attempts to share your personal information with any third party.

* * *

#### Opting-Out Personally Identifiable Consumer Information

You have the right to ask for information deletion at anytime from our database. You can email us at [info@windowsestimator.com](mailto:info@windowsestimator.com), and we will delete your data from our servers completely. However, you need to communicate your opting-out request with the contractors who receive your quote request and our partner who matched you with those contractors. The partner will communicate with you directly and offers clear way to opt-out from their systems.

* * *

#### Our Commitment To Data Security

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. For example, we carry out software update for our servers software including but not limited to the database server, web server and operating system.

* * *

#### How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information

You can email us [info@windowsestimator.com](mailto:info@windowsestimator.com) including the correct information, and we will be happy to pass it to our partners to carry out the contractor-home owner matching process, and update it in our database systems.

* * *

#### Your Consent

By using ****windowsestimator.com**** , you consent to the terms of our Online Privacy Policy. Should the Online Privacy Policy change, we intend to take every reasonable step to ensure that these changes are brought to your attention by posting all changes prominently on our web site for a reasonable period of time and by amending this privacy policy.

* * *

#### Contact Us

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please send us an email at [info@windowsestimator.com](mailto:info@windowsestimator.com).
